investingdaily.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Investing Daily

Your privacy concerns are important to us. We’ve created this statement in order to fully demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices that we use when you’re visiting our Website.

**Information We Collect**

We collect personal information to provide our Services as well as some non-personal information about visitors to the Website. We use the term “personal information” to mean (1) information that can be used to determine, distinguish or trace an individual’s identity, such as name, e-mail address, address, phone number, age, and (2) any other information that is linked or linkable to an individual, such as medical and employment information.

_We collect personal and non-personal information in the following ways:_

**Personal information you give us:** We may obtain personal information about you ONLY if you elect to give us that information. We may request personal information to provide you our Services or enable you to purchase goods or services available on the Website. Types of personal information we may ask you to provide may include the following:

  * Name
  * Zip code
  * Country
  * Telephone number
  * E-mail address
  * Mailing address
  * Credit card number and expiration date (for online purchases)

You must provide us with a valid email address at all times, as that will be how we communicate with you regarding all aspects of the Website, Program, and Services.

**Non-personal Information we may collect:** We may also collect information or data in a form that does not by itself permit us to associate it with any specific individual, which we treat as “non-personal information” in this Policy. For example, we may collect information regarding visitors the Website to help us provide more useful information to visitors and Program participants and to understand which parts of the Website and our Services are of most interest.

**E-mail Address**

Your e-mail address is unique and when linked to your subscription, gives an added level of security when you access your account. We do not collect your e-mail address unless you specifically provide it to us.

When you register online, we offer a selection of e-mail preferences and services from which you may choose the type of e-mail you would prefer to receive. Preferences include market updates, free e-zines, service-related matters, special offers relating to your subscription, special offers from the publisher and sometimes offers from affiliate companies that we believe may be of interest to you.

You may modify your selections at any time from the Subscriber Services section of the Website via the “My Account” link. Additionally, every promotional e-mail we send includes a way for you to opt out of receiving similar messages in the future.

**Postal Address**

If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about new products and services or upcoming events. You may also receive postal mailings from other reputable organizations that offer products and services that we think may be of interest to you. Outside of these organizations, we will not disclose any information unless required to do so by law or other regulatory authority.

**Telephone Numbers**

It’s very rare that we might contact you by telephone. But we may do so if we have a question about your order or if we discover an opportunity that may interest you. We do not rent your telephone number to other organizations.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a data file that is written to a computer’s hard drive when you visit certain Websites. We use cookies on this Website to authenticate your user name and password and to maintain the login for the duration of your visit. If you do not want us to send cookies to your browser, you can use your browser options to reject cookies or notify you when a website tries to put cookies into your browser. If you reject cookies, there may be features of the Website and Services provided on the Website that you cannot use.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies on our website to serve ads based on your prior visits to Investing Daily or other websites. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

**Sponsors, Advertisers, And Links**

This Website may provide links to third-party Websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. On these sites, other companies may collect personally identifiable information about you. For instance, we collect available demographics info from Google Analytics in order to further improve the user of experience of our website for our members. We do not share or expose any of that data publicly. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those parties and Websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Correspondence**

E-mail is not privacy protected. Messages traveling through the Internet using e-mail processes are subject to viewing, alteration and copying by potentially anyone on the Internet. We encourage you to send confidential correspondence only through the channels provided within this Website.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not provide products or services for children, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. In the event that we learn we have collected personal information about a child, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We use personal information collected online to best provide and administer our Services, purchasing a product from the Website, and provide information, such as sending marketing communications and newsletters. Investing Daily will only retain and use your personal information for the purposes for which such personal information is collected.

**Your Data Protection Rights Under The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:

  * If you wish to access, correct, update, or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us.
  * In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us.
  * You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “preferences” links in the footer of any emails we send you.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
